# NABILA NORDIN

## • DETAILS •

Klang Malaysia +6019-245 3225 nabilanordin87@gmail.com

## o SKILLS o

Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel
WIZ Accounting System
ACCPAC Accounting System
UBS Accounting System

## PROFILE

An Account Executive with 9 years of working experience within private sector organization. Specialization areas in property developer organization. Recently up skill with further knowledge in Data Analytics and interested to explore new career opportunities and new challenges.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Account Executive at Nadayu Properties Berhad, Selangor

April 2021 — July 2021

- Manage accounting system including preparation of full set of accounts, bank reconciliation, book keeping and financial statement.
- Ensure management accounts are accurately prepared on a monthly basis.
- Prepare and monitor balance sheet and cash flow.
- Liaise with auditors and tax consultants.
- Provide safekeeping including important documents eg: financial records.
- Perform other related duties as assigned by the head of department.

#### Account ExecutiveatUEM Sunrise Berhad, Kuala Lumpur

June 2013 — January 2020

- -Report directly to the Deputy Senior Manager in the Finance Department.
- Verify and ensure all approved supplier invoices and statutory payment are paid within the credit term/ statutory deadline to avoid any penalty.
- Manage month end closing and bank reconciliation and ensure the transaction are taken up in the following month.
- Project accrual and provision postings for all operation and development expenses and accurately posted all into the journals.
- Maintain and manage fixed asset register.
- Oversee cash flow and monitor the payment for the month and inter company transaction within the group of companies.
- Engage with internal/ external auditor during preliminary and year end audit process.
- Liaise with external parties such as Company Secretary, Tax Agent, Bankers, authorities (IRB or Custom) for all the required statutory report.
- Assist in computing tax computation and drafting audit report.
- Undertake ad-hoc assignment given by the superior.

# Account Executive cum AdminatIdaman Unggul Berhad, Selangor

January 2012 — May 2013

- Report directly to the Finance Manager in the Finance Department.
- Keeping track of all payment and expenditures and maintaining accurate and complete records.
- Ensure all approved supplier invoices are paid within the credit term.
- Manage month end closing and bank reconciliation and ensure all transaction are taken up in the following month.

- Accountable for general administrative work.
- Undertake ad-hoc assignment given by the superior.

# Account Assistant (contract)atEsprit De Corp (M) Sdn Bhd, Selangor

September 2011 — December 2011

- Calculated daily sales record.
- Assisted in issuance of cheque to suppliers.
- Key in database.

# Global Support ExecutiveatHSBC Electronic Data Processing (M) Sdn Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

June 2010 — September 2011

- Responsible for Annual Client Risk for HSBC's client.
- Monitor daily basis business transaction, Account Payable and payment function.
- Obtaining document required by Relationship Manager and undertakes the necessary action due diligence checking.
- Responsible for account opening for HSBC's client in Hong Kong region.

# **INTERNSHIPS**

## IntershipatSoon & Co, Kuala Lumpur

December 2008 — May 2009

- Assist in planning and performing statutory audit for client
- Checking client's account and perform journal entry if necessary
- Prepare full set of audit report to client

# EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Accounting (Hons), Universiti Tenaga Nasional (UNITEN), Pahang July 2006 — July 2010

Data Analytics Full Reskilling Programme, Air Asia Academy in partnership with Google Platform, Kuala Lumpur

November 2022 — November 2022

# CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Excel 2013 Advanced, New Horizons Computer Learning Centers
August 2020 — August 2020

# **1** REFERENCES

• References available upon request